Good Hair is a documentary, comedy film directed by Jeff Stilson.
An exposé of comic proportions that only Chris Rock could pull off, GOOD HAIR visits beauty salons and hairstyling battles, scientific laboratories and
Indian temples to explore the way hairstyles impact the activities, pocketbooks, sexual relationships, and self-esteem of the black community.
Self, played by Maya Angelou.
Self, played by Chris Rock.
Self, played by Nia Long.
Self, played by Vanessa Bell Calloway.
Self, played by Ice-T.
Self - Hair Battle Contestant, played by Tanya Crumel.
Good Hair is a 2009 American documentary film directed by Jeff Stilson and produced by Chris
Rock Productions and HBO Films, starring and narrated by comedian Chris Rock.
Premiering at the Sundance Film Festival on January 18, 2009, Good Hair had a limited release to theaters in the
United States by Roadside Attractions on October 9, 2009, and opened across the country on October 23.
The film centers on the issue of how African-American women have
perceived their hair and historically styled it.
The film explores the modern-day styling industry for black women, images of what is considered acceptable and desirable
for African-American women's hair in the United States, and their relation to African-American culture.
The film explores themes of introspective, factual, hilarious.
The tone is lighthearted.